Problem:  Write a program to transform SQL query into its equivalent relational algebraic expression.

LOGS:

Solution:
	Step 1:
		Identify types of Relational Operations.		[]
		(i) Select						[done]
		(ii) Project						[done]
		(iii) Union						[no]
		(iv) Set difference					[no]
		(v) Join						[done]
		(vi) Rename						[NA]
		(vii) Intersection					[done][derivable]
			Can be implemented as Set Difference: A |^^| B = (A - (A - B))
		(viii) Natural join					[done][derivable]
			Can be implemented as Cartesian Product: A |X| B = (π(a1,a2,..,an)(A X B))
		(ix) Theta join						[done][derivable]
			Can be implemented as Cartesian Product: A |X| B = (π(a1,a2,..,an)(σ(c)(A X B)))
		(x) Assignment						[NA]
	
	Step 2:
		-> Syntax checking was implemented in last assignment
		-> Just convert the queries to relational algebra
		-> Set an algorithm
			-> Set an order of selected operations: 
				(i)Projection (pi) [Save the list of attriutes separately]
				(ii)Orderby (Gamma) [Save the orderby attributes]
				(iii)Groupby (Latin-G) [Save the aggregate functions separately]
				(iv)Conditions (Sigma) [Check the index of where and push conditions with connectors to a list]
				(v)Join (Join symbol) [Check the index of join and push theta conditions to corresponding thetajoinlist]
			-> Print the relational algebra in the same order using the lists saved in last step and unicode characters
		-> Bug Reports:
			(i) Issue: Syntax?
				   Done in last assignment!
				   Resolved$
			(ii) Issue: Python printing annoying line breaks?
				    Use the end tag in print (stackoverflow)
				    Resolved$
			(iii) Issue: Spaces inside keywords like 'group by'
				     Truncate spaces between keywords in preprocessing
				     Resolved$
			(iv) Issue: Unified separator algorithm becoming clumsy due to too much variables?
				    Separate 'join' , 'where', 'orderby', 'groupby' algos to make it readable
				    Resolved$
			(v) Issue: Code not readable?
				   Putting necessary comments
				   Resolved$
			(vi) Issue: Union, Intersection still not implemented?
				    Can't implement until recursive queries are not implemented
				    &&&&&&&&$
			(vii) Issue: Recursive Queries?
				     &&&&&&&&$
			(viii) Issue: join using commas?
				      Implement the else part in the join module
				      Resolved$	
				     
	Step 3: Testing:
		-> Created Test file "input.txt"				[done]
		-> Fed into parser to check the validity			[done]
		-> Write manually into notebook to explain			[done]
		-> Think of correct answers and check, then report bugs		[done]
		-> To be Evaluated on March 4th 2019				[done]