Problem:  Write a program to check whether a schedule is conflict serializable or not by creating a precedence graph. The schedule should 
	  contain more than 2 transactions.
Deadline: 2 weeks from March 11, 2019

Solution:
	Step 1: Input Parsing:
		Set the input format for schedule.
		Input format will be as follows:
		(i) Everything will be in chronological order, that is by operation which are performed earlier will appear earlier.
		(ii) 'r-x(a)' will mean a read operation, where 'x' is the transaction id and 'a' is the data item.
		(iii) 'w-x(a)' will mean a write operation, where 'x' is the transaction id and 'a' is the data item.
		(iv) If there are 'n' transactions in the schedule then it should strictly be numbered from '1' to 'n' only.
		For eg. r-1(a) r-2(a) r-3(b) w-1(a) w-2(a) w-3(b)
	Step 2: Algorithm:
		Set the algorithm to check conflict serializability.
		(i) Create a directed graph by parsing the input as a schedule, where each transaction will be a vertex and if there is a
		    conflicting operation from transaction 'i' to transaction 'j' then add a directed edge from 'i' to 'j'. O(n^2)
		(ii) Check for any cycle in the above di-graph by using a DFS and coloring algorithm to check for back edges. O(n)
		(iii) If there is a cycle then the schedule is not conflict serializable, otherwise it is.
		(iv) Front End: Show the result as well as the di-graph on a png image using pydotplus.

	Step 3: Bug Reporting:
		Issue:
			How to take input: 
			sol: referred geeksforgeeks to check the input format and made certain modifications too.
			$$Resolved$$
		Issue: 
			How to visualize the graph:
			sol: referred pydotplus to create visual graphs and printing their png
			$$Resolved$$
		Issue: 
			How to detect cycle in the graph:
			sol: -> Find back edge(edge from a node to itself or to a node which is currently in the recursion stack of DFS ,i.e.,
			     an ancestor of the node) in the graph. Keep 2 arrays, visited[] for DFS and RecStack[] for checking if a node
			     is currently present in the recursion stack or not.
			     -> Implement this as an utility function for all the DFS trees present in the forest.
			$$Resolved$$
		Issue:
			How to do a Topological sort:
			sol: -> Can be done only if the graph is directed and acyclic
			     -> Call a DFS recursively for all the DFS trees in the forest. Keep a temporary stack which will help in getting
			     the sorted order of nodes. For a node first recursively call topological sorting for all its adjacent vertices, 
			     then push it to the temporary stack.
			     -> Print the stack finally, after every node in the graph has been visited.
			     -> Implement all of this in python.
			$$Resolved$$
		Issue: 
			Code is cumbersome and very long.
			sol: Modularize it into several files, and make comments.
			$$Resolved$$
		Issue:
			Make the cycles colorful. Put steps in topological sorting and color them differently.
			sol: Update the DFSutil of isCyclic() function.
			$$Resolved$$
		
	Step 4: Testing:
		-> Created Test file "input.txt"				[done]
		-> Write manually into notebook to explain			[done]
		-> Think of correct answers and check, then report bugs		[done]
		-> To be Evaluated on April 1, 2019				[done]